export const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Which article of the Indian Constitution guarantees the right to education for all children, including girls?",
      options: ["Article 21", "Article 15", "Article 45", "Article 14"],
      correctAnswer: "Article 15"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is the name of the government program launched in India to promote girls' education?",
      options: ["Beti Bachao, Beti Padhao", "Swachh Bharat Abhiyan", "Make in India", "Jan Dhan Yojana"],
      correctAnswer: "Beti Bachao, Beti Padhao"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What percentage of seats in educational institutions are reserved for girls under the Right to Education Act in India?",
      options: ["20%", "25%", "30%", "35%"],
      correctAnswer: "25%"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "In which year was the Right of Children to Free and Compulsory Education Act (RTE) enacted in India?",
      options: ["2005", "2010", "2015", "2020"],
      correctAnswer: "2010"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Which organization primarily oversees the implementation of girls' education initiatives in India?",
      options: ["Ministry of Health and Family Welfare", "Ministry of Women and Child Development", "Ministry of Human Resource Development", "Ministry of Rural Development"],
      correctAnswer: "Ministry of Human Resource Development"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the dropout rate among girls in India, according to recent statistics?",
      options: ["20%", "30%", "40%", "50%"],
      correctAnswer: "40%"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which Indian state has the highest female literacy rate?",
      options: ["Kerala", "Bihar", "Uttar Pradesh", "Rajasthan"],
      correctAnswer: "Kerala"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is the primary reason for the low enrollment of girls in schools in rural areas of India?",
      options: ["Lack of interest in education", "Poverty and financial constraints", "Inadequate school infrastructure", "Cultural norms and societal restrictions"],
      correctAnswer: "Cultural norms and societal restrictions"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Which international organization has partnered with India to support girls' education initiatives?",
      options: ["World Bank", "International Monetary Fund", "United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)", "Asian Development Bank"],
      correctAnswer: "United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is the name of the flagship scholarship program in India aimed at promoting higher education among girls from economically weaker sections?",
      options: ["Kanya Kelavani Yojana", "Pragati Scholarship Scheme", "Sukanya Samriddhi Yojana", "Beti Bachao Scholarship Program"],
      correctAnswer: "Beti Bachao Scholarship Program"
    },
  ];